The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Reporting to Grand Elder
Elders Pu Lin, Gu Cheng and Kun Sang
have requested reinforcements.
Qian Kun\NFighting Evil Sect Grand Elder\NMiddle stage Core Formation
Grand Elder,
should we go ?
Our Fighting Evil Sect's territory
is not to be messed with.
Pu Lin !
This isn't a regular Foundation Establishment cultivator.
This guy is about to
enter the Core Formation stage !
After one day and one night,
my flying sword's attacks are no longer as effective.
My Ji Realm is only able to injure them
but not kill them.
It seems I only have a single card left.
Even if the Underworld Ice Flame is strong,
it's like a tree without roots.
Using it like this will consume the flame
at a very fast pace.
I have no choice but to risk it...
Grand Elder !
Three more Core Formations have arrived...
The leader is at Middle stage Core Formation.
Now that reinforcements have arrived
I can't risk shattering my Core embryo
to kill them anymore.
Little brat,
you killed an Elder of our Fighting Evil Sect.
No matter how far you flee,
we will still kill you !
I have one last idea.
Although it will be dangerous,
it will all be over
if I succeed.
Faster, I must go faster !
It's been 3 years
and I still haven't heard from him...
Back then, he saved my life.
And then he promised
to send me back to the Burning Fire Alliance.
I wonder if he will ever come back...
Senior !
Senior...
What's wrong ?
What happened ?
Little brat,
why did you stop running ?
Wu Liu\NFighting Evil Sect Elder\NEarly stage Core Formation
Da Tou (Big Head)\NFighting Evil Sect Elder\NEarly stage Core Formation
That young woman we just saw
belongs to me !
It just happened that I needed a cultivation furnace !
When did such a formation appear here ?
Since this formation can summon a dragon,
it can't be ordinary...
Kun Sang,
try using your Thousand Peaks Seal Stamp.
This really is a good formation...
Fellow Elders,
let's attack this formation together !
This is the Great Annihilation Talisman ?
If not for your Flood Dragon armor,
I would've died by now.
His talisman is very powerful
with his Middle stage Core Formation cultivation.
This is a grade 5 pill furnace.
Refine the Heaven Separating Pill as fast as you can.
This...
Are they chasing you
because of this furnace !?
No.
We only have one way out now.
You must refine the pill
so I can reach Core Formation.
We won't walk out of this cave alive
if I'm not Core Formation.
I must succeed...
If the formation breaks,
it will all be over !
Break !
I failed...
I can't just give up like this !
I still have the Demon Blood Vine.
We still have time...
Senior !
Senior...
This is a Heaven Separating Pill made from Demon Blood Vine.
Its effect isn't... as good.
But !
How much longer
can the formation hold ?
If 5 Core Formations keep attacking it like that,
no more than 4 days.
I will reach Core Formation as soon as possible.
3 days later
This formation is no joke,
it didn't break after 3 days.
Da Tou,
if you want that woman, you need to deserve her.
Break !
The formation... is gone...
There's actually another formation !
Everyone, let me handle this !
At this distance,
I will be able to trap that brat
by using the Immortal Trapping Net the moment he walks out.
Is this what you want ?
I didn't expect that little bastard would be able to buy
that pill furnace for 100 000 high-quality spirit stones !
Give it to me, little girl.
Grand Elder, this pill furnace belongs to me now !
I will definitely repay you later, what do you think ?
You wish !
Explode !
How dare you destroy that pill furnace !?
Since you're looking for death,
I shall grant your wish !
He saved my life in the first place...
I am just repaying him...
Step back !
He killed a Core Formation cultivator in an instant !?
What kind of monster is he !?
Wait for me.
From now on,
I'm the strongest person below Nascent Soul.
Wang Lin\NEarly stage Core Formation
If none of you are hiding your cultivation
then you can all
die.
Run !
I have never been afraid
within South Dipper City.
This is the first
and only time in my life
that I've been afraid.
Let's go.
Where ?
We have some people to kill.
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?